[{"answer": "Well, praying does help.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 15, "question": "Is it going to come to praying again?", "qSentId": 14}, {"answer": "At one point, we started talking about the tenth anniversary of 9/11.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 30, "question": "What was the most striking part of it from your point of view?", "qSentId": 29}, {"answer": "He's got a lot more gray hair.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "How had he changed physically and in himself and his demeanor to you?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "Has the election proper started now, do you think?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, my overview is that president is seeing the impact of the results that he's had.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "What's your overview of what the president is up to and where he stands?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "I don't know yet.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "Would you agree with that?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "I don't think I've changed my thinking about it very much.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 134, "question": "Are you feeling more inclined to run now or less inclined?", "qSentId": 133}, {"answer": "Well, because the only way you're going to increase confidence in the American economy which China is worried about and the rest of the world is to stop us from spending money.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "What is wrong with that?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "I haven't really focused in on it.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "Let me ask you -- if you don't run, Rudy, which of the candidates at the moment is the one that you would feel most comfortable being the nominee for the Republicans?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "Sure is.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 178, "question": "Is it conceivable, do you think, that a Tea Party candidate like a Michele Bachmann could end up being the nominee?", "qSentId": 177}, {"answer": "End of September, I'd say, would be the latest.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "Funny, Rudy, what's the latest you could leave it personally to make a decision as to whether or not you're going to run?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "I think, you know, like we see with Wolf Blitzer today, the president is pumped up.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "How did he seem to you?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "I think he has great marks.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "If you were his teacher and you were doing a school report after three years, good marks and where could he be better?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "I agree with Warren Buffett.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "So, you agree with Warren Buffett?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "The rich should get pay more?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 233, "question": "Since John Kennedy said ask not what your country can do for you, what you're going to do for your country?", "qSentId": 232}, {"answer": "Well, I think he's already, you know, made spectacular gains.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "So he's got his work cut out, hasn't he?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "I think the president, has much better ways than me as a producer.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "And how do you fix it with jobs, do you think?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "Apple, Google -- I am.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 282, "question": "You are hiring more staff?", "qSentId": 281}, {"answer": "She's tall.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "Is this about Michelle Obama, isn't it?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "The first week that Sandra and Ryan did the proposal, \"Funny or Die,\" they did 600,000.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "But the crucial battle theme, you're a competitive man, is you're very near to beating Sandra Bullock and Ryan Reynolds in the number of people who viewed this, right?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "I don't find it negative at all.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "It's a negative thing, isn't it?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "I do really?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "You do.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "Do I really anger you?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "Let me ask you.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "How did we get here?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "I believe in this superior being, a God.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "How did we get here?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "But answer to something -- saying we can't understand it is not an answer.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "Because I never hear an atheist give me any answers to how did we get here and what happens at the end of our lives?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "How do you think we got here?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "Well, nothing.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "What do you think happens when whether you die?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "How scared of you are of 1890.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "What do you think happens to you?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "1890, yes.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "1890?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "You weren't alive then, right?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "Is that a horror to you?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "I'm not horrified by any thought of dying, because I believe you go on to a celestial place which is wonderful.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 451, "question": "So why is 2090 any worse than that?", "qSentId": 450}, {"answer": "I come back to the issue of creation.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "Where is your evidence of a celestial place?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "No, no, no, not at all.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "We're all a bit crazy, a bit nuts?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "No, because that is not the type of God I believe in.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "Yeah, Thor?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "Because it's not the same thing.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "No, but I have an absolute respect for anybody from any religion that has a spiritual and religious conviction and belief in a god-like entity in their lives.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "Even though there are different rules?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "I am dying.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "What if you were dying, hypothetically?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "Do you know this?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "Because there is nothing I like doing more than my show.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 573, "question": "Why would you live in Las Vegas?", "qSentId": 572}, {"answer": "At least I got a prayer.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 591, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 590}, {"answer": "I always seem to think that the most important thing is individuals.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 600, "question": "What's the answer?", "qSentId": 599}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 658, "question": "They do?", "qSentId": 657}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 662, "question": "On a mass scale?", "qSentId": 661}, {"answer": "I think.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 664, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 663}, {"answer": "What I would do is I think make the government much, much smaller.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 668, "question": "ORGAN: What is the one thing you would do, if you were president, to get Americans back to work?", "qSentId": 667}, {"answer": "Moxie.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 695, "question": "Moxie Crime Fighter?", "qSentId": 694}, {"answer": "Better than that.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 717, "question": "Is she old enough to realize what you've done?", "qSentId": 716}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 738, "question": "Does it feel like a marriage to you?", "qSentId": 737}, {"answer": "ILLETTE: Wonderfully.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 752, "question": "And how do you get on now?", "qSentId": 751}, {"answer": "About twice a year we go out socially together.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 760, "question": "Do you socialize away from work?", "qSentId": 759}, {"answer": "No, no, no.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 764, "question": "Do you do all the talking?", "qSentId": 763}, {"answer": "More so than me.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 768, "question": "So he's perfectly garrulous when you have dinner?", "qSentId": 767}, {"answer": "I would pray, I think, for more perfect knowledge.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 776, "question": "If I could give you the power of prayer, I awarded it to you, what would you pray for?", "qSentId": 775}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110816pmt", "aSentId": 784, "question": "Why surprising?", "qSentId": 783}]